Finding Aid for the Paul Jordan Smith Papers LSC.0267
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence
  - Fo
    - Follett, Wilson., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Forest Park Foundation, Peoria, Illinois., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Forsyth, Harold P., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - The Forum., 2 items. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Foster, George Burnam, 1858-1918., 1 item (photograph) (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Fox, George O., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Fox, Maude A., 2 items. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Fox, Rosalea., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Ford, Lillian., 4 items. (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Fowler, Gene, 1890-1960., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Fr
    - Francis, W.W., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Franks, Danforth Wilson., 2 items. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Franks, W.W., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Free World Association., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Freitag, George H., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Freund, Philip., 2 items. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Friday Morning Club., 10 items. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Friedman, Stuart., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Frink, Maurice., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Frye, Burton., 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Freeman, Luther., 14 items. (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Fuller, Catherine & Gene., 3 items. (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Ga
    - Galambos, Anne., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Gard, Wayne., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Garth, Morris., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Gazzam, Charles., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Gaer, Joseph, 1897-., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Gardner, Erle Stanley, 1889-1970., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Garland, Hamlin, 1860-1940., n.d.-1933.; 12 items. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Garland, Hamlin, 1934-1935.; 11 items. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Garland, Hamlin, 1936-1939.; 11 items. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Gaselee, Sir Stephen, 1882-1943., 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Ge
    - Gekle, William F., 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Getz, Mrs. M.E., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Gerson, Theodore Perceval, 1872-1960., 1925-1947.; 8 items. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Gerson, Theodore Perceval, 1953-1960.; 11 items. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Gi - Gl
    - Giddings, Margaret., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Gilbert, Helen E., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Gilbert, Stuart., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Giles, Janice Holt., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Gilmer, Betty., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Gipson, James Herrick, Sr., 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Glenn, May., 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Giacomini, Lynwood., 3 items. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Gilligan, Edmund., 3 items. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Glass, Maude Emily, 1897-., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 13a)
  - Go
    - Godfrey, Marie., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Gold Medal Books., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Goldsmith, Alfred F., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Gordon, Wilmot S., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Goldstone, Adrian., 3 items. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Gollancz, Sir Israel, 1864-1930., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Goldwater, Barry., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Goodspeed, Edgar Johnson, 1871-1962., 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Gr - Gu
    - Granada Shoppes & Studios., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Grand Hotel du Louvre., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Grant, Bruce., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Gray, Blanche., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Graye, John A., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Graye, Margaret., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Greenwood, Annie Pike., 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Griffith, C.H., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - The Grolier Club., 2 items. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Gruber, Frank, 1904-., 1 item. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation., 3 items. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Guy, Earl, 1943-1956.; 15 items. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Guy, Earl, 1957-1965.; 16 items. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Guy, Earl, 1965-1967.; 15 items. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Guy, Earl, 1967-1970.; 14 items. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Ha
    - Hackett, Helen., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Hagedorn, Hermann., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Halliday, Bernard., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Hamilton National Bank., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Hammon, Milton E., Jr., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Han, Yu-Shan., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Hansen, Isabel & Kelly., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Haeckel, Ernst., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Hanna, Phil Townsend, 1896-1957., 6 items. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Har - Hat
    - Harding-Edgar, B., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Harris, Bernice Kelly., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Harris, John., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Harris, Roger., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Harrison, Benjamin S., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Haskell, H.J., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Hatch, Mary A., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Harcourt, Brace & Company., 6 items. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Hardy, Thomas, 1840-1928., 8 items. (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Scope and Contents note
      (signed by Hardy's wife, Florence)
    - Harper & Brothers., 4 items. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Harrison, Dorothy Beard., 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Hartley, Annabel., 5 items. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Hartmann, Sadakichi, 1867-1944., 5 items. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Hau - Haz
    - Hauline, Maurice A., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Hauser, Myrtle., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Haviland-Taylor, Katharine., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Hayward, Max E., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Hazel, John., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Hawthorne, Edith Garrignes (Mrs. Julian)., 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 11a)
    - Hays, Will H, Jr, 1879-1954., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - He - Hep
    - Heilman, Tirrell., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Heinecke, Joan Hazel., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Helene Wurlitzer Foundation., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Henderson, Archibald, 1879-1963., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Henry, Darold J., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Henry, Robert S., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Henry E. Huntington Library., 9 items. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Her - Hez
    - Hermitage House, Incorporated., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Hertz, Emanuel., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Heslop, Janie Miller Wilson., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Hess, Juanita Callicott., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Hersholt, Jean, 1886-., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Hi
    - Hicky, Daniel Whitehead., 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Hill, Eldon C., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Hilton, James, 1900-1954., 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Hines, Duncan, 1880-., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Hinton, Percival., 8 items. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Ho - Hoo
    - Hodge, Betty., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Hodgin, E. Stanton., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Hodgdon, Charles., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Hoffman, Frank., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Holden, Harold M., M.D., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Hollings, Frank., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Höltgen, Karl Josef., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Hooghwinkel, Nora., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Henry E. Holt & Company., 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Honnold Library, Claremont, California., 10 items. (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Honnold Library, Claremont, California., 10 items. (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Honnold Library, Claremont, California., 10 items. (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Hor - Hu
    - Horan, Thomas., 2 items. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Howes, C., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Huber, M.H., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Hull, Virginia., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Hunter, Robert., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Hynes, Frank J., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Hougland, Willard., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Hoyt, Helen, 1887-., 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Hughes, Rupert, 1872-1956., 6 items. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Hunt, Rockwell Dennis, 1868-., 3 items. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Huntington Hartford Foundation., 12 items. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Huntington Hartford Foundation., 4 items. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Huntington Hartford Foundation Monthly Newsletter., 29 items. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - I
    - Illinois State Historical Society., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Immaculate Heart College., 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Ingram, Dora., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Ireland, Francis Melvin., 8 items. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Isgrigg, Helen Bierce., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Ja - Je
    - Jackson, Adalyn Gunn., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Jamison, Della., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Jessen, J.M., 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Jewish Peoples Committee., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Jackson, Holbrook, 1874-1948., 4 items. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Jacoby, Grover., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Jacoby, Neil Herman, 1909-., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - James, C.L.R., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Jeffers, Una (Call)., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Jennings, John E., Jr., 3 items. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Jo
    - Johnson, Earl S., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Johnson, Katharine McCallie., 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Jones, Clifford E., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Jones, Elizabeth Sheridan., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Jones, Nard., 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Jones, William Corey., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Jordan, Mrs. Glen Thomas, Jr., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Jones, Idwal, 1890-., 3 items. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Jones, Louise Seymour., 4 items. (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Jordan, Elizabeth Garver, 1867-1947., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Jordan, Oscar P., 8 items. (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Jordan, T. Ashby., 10 items. (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Jordan, T. Ashby., 11 items. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Ka
    - Kamal, Ahmad., 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Kaminski, Jo., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Kane, Linda., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Kaup, Elizabeth Dewing., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Kane, Harnett T., 3 items. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Ke
    - Kemp, Edward., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Kennerley, Mitchell., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Kerlan, Irvin., 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Kerr, Willis., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Keith, Joseph Joel., 5 items. (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Kelly, Edith Summers., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Ki - Kil
    - Kibbey, Aloyse., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Kilpatrick, James J., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Kilroy, John K., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Kim - Kiz
    - Kimble, G. Eleanor., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - King, Kenneth M., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - King's Arms Hotel., 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Kingston, Natali G., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Kinnaird, Clark., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Kinslow, Mary., 1 item. (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Kirby, Geraldine (Kelly)., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Kirkbride, Ronald de Levington, 1912-., 6 items. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Kirsch, Robert R., 1922-., 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Kissin, Rita., 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Kl - Kn
    - Klatt, Mrs. E.L., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Klingberg, Elizabeth W., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Klingberg, Frank Wysor, 1919-., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Knight, Bertha M., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Knight, Ruth Adams., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Knox, George., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Alfred A. Knopf Incorporated., 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Knox College., 9 items. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Ko - Kr
    - Kosa, Emil J., Jr., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Kowalewski, Edmond., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Kraemer, J.C., Jr., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Krey, Laura L., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Kromer, Anne., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Kohn, Walter, 1956-1960.; 9 items. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Kohn, Walter, 1960-1961.; 10 items. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Kohn, Walter, 1962-1963.; 11 items. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Kohn, Walter, 1963-1969.; 12 items. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Kreider, Florence W., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Kreymborg, Alfred, 1883-., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - La
    - LaChance, Donald., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Lagard, Garald., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - The Lapidary Journal., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Latimer, Jargery., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Laudermilk, Jerome., 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Luaritzen, Jonreed, 1902-., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Lavender, David Sievert, 1910-., 12 items. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Le
    - Lee, Berta Hammon., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Lee, Clark., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Leisen, Clara., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Lewis, Jessica., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Lewman, Mrs. P., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Leighton, Margaret., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Le Prade, Ruth., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Lewis, Lucile., 4 items. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Lewisohn, Ludwig, 1883-., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Li
    - Lieber, Maxim., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Lincoln Printers., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Lindberg, Eddie., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Lindsey, Henrietta B., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Literary Clipping Service., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - J.J. Little & Ives Company., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Little, Brown & Company., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Lin, Yu-t'ang, 1895-., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Lo - Lop
    - Lodge, George C., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Logan, Libbie., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Long, Eula., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Long Beach City College., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Long Beach Public Library., 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Longmans, Green & Company., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Lockmiller, David Alexander, 1906-., 8 items. (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Lor - Los
    - Lord, David H., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Los Angeles Press Club., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Los Angeles Public Library., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Los Angeles State College., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Los Angeles Times., 3 items. (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Lot - Lu
    - Lott, Merrill R., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Lowry, H.H., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Lukei, Vesta Nickerson., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Lundberg, Dan., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Luxford, Earle M., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Ludwig, Emil, 1881-1948., 10 items. (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Ludwig, Emil., 14 items. (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Lummis, Charles Fletcher, 1859-1928., 2 items. (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Luther, Mark Lee, 1872-., 1 item. (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Lyman, W.W., 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Mc
    - Robert M. McBride Company., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McCain, Irene., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McCall, Bertha., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McCardell, Roy L., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McClure, Robert E., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McCutcheon, Evelyn S., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - MacDonald, Helen L., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - McCall's., 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - McFarlane, Peter Clark, 1871-1924., 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - McK
    - McKelvey, Raymond., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - MacKenna, Kenneth., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McKenzie, Dorothy C., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McLaughlin, Mary E., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McLean, Edward., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Macloghlin, John., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McMullen, Emily., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - McKay, Alexander., 10 items. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - McKay, Alexander., 10 items. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - McKinley, Arthur Patch, 1871-1958., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - MacLeod, LeRoy., 9 items. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - The MacMillan Company., 12 items. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - McWilliams, Carey, 1905-., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Ma - Mal
    - Mabbott, Thomas Olive., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Madsen, Walter., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Maid's Head Hotel., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Mais, G.M.S., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Malcolm, George A., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Malcolmson, David., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Maldonoado, Fernando A., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Males, Stephanie V., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Malone, Dumas, 1892-., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Mackey, William D., 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Mam - Mar
    - Mamet, Louis., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Mandell, Irving., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Mann, Stella Terrill., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Marador Publishing Company., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - A.N. Marquis Company., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Marrs, Edwin W., Jr., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Martin, Ernest., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Martin, Lester., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Manfred, Frederick Feikema, 1912-., 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Martin, Woodfin B., 11 items. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Mas - Me
    - Mason, Gregory., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Maunder, John., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Maverick, Lewis A., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Mayfield, John S., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Merlin, Milton., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Merlin, Sallie., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Messner, Julian., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Methodist Historical Society., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Mëyr, Berl ben., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Mencken, Henry Louis, 1880-1956., 7 items. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Mertins, Marshall Louis, 1885-., 5 items. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Merwin, Walter S., 1912-., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Mi
    - Michigan Lapidary Supply & Research Company., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Mighell, Marjorie Holmes., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Miller, Caroline., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Miller, Helen., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Miller, Sylvia., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Miller, Sarah., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - The Mineralogist., 2 items. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Minnesota, University of., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Minoff, Natalie., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Minter, Mary, Miles, 1902-., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Mitgang, Herbert., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Millard, Alice (Parsons), 1873-1938., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Millard, Christopher (Sclater), 1872-1927., 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Miller, G.H., 4 items. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Mitchell, Margaret, 1900-1949., 5 items. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Mo - My
    - Mock, Bill., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Moorland Hotel., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Morain, Lloyd L., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Morgan, Willard D., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - William Morrow & Company, Incorporated., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Morse, Harriet P., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Moser, Paul., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Mott, Howard S., Jr., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Mowery, Bob Lee., 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Moxley, Verna., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Muir, H.B., 2 items, 4 bookplates. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      General note
      Book-plates--Specimens.
    - Mulhauser, Margaret., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Myers, Elsie., 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Monaghan, Jay., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Monlux, Herbert., 10 items. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Moody, Ralph, 1898-., 4 items. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Moore, Ellen., 12 items. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Moore, John G., 1900-., 1955-1964.; 11 items. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Moore, John G., 1964-1966.; 11 items. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Moore, John G., 1967-1970.; 9 items. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Moore, Merrill, 1903-1957., 3 items. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Moore, Sarah., 6 items. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Morgenthau, H., Jr., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Morley, Christopher Darlington, 1890-1957., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Murad, Orlene., 4 items. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Na - Ne
    - Naftzger, Claire., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Nevada, University of., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - New Age Press Incorporated., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - New Directions., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - New Mexico Highlands University., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - New York Life Insurance Company., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Nathan, Robert, 1894-., n.d.-1953.; 14 items. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Nathan, Robert, 1957-1971.; 14 items. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Neider, Charles., 10 items. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Neutra, Richard Joseph, 1892-1970., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Newton, Edward Alfred, 1863-1940., 14 items. (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Ni - No
    - Nichols, Fred S., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Niedermann, Alfred., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Niles, Blair (Rice)., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Nitschke, Earl R., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Norris, Natalie., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Nitze, William Albert, 1876-1957., 2 items. (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1913-., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Nockian Society., 3 items. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - North, Sterling, 1906-., 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - W.W. Norton & Company., 6 items. (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - O - Ol
    - Obayashi, Bud., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Occidental College., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - O'Connor, R.S., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Ohio State University., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Old George Hotel., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - O'Flaherty, Terence., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Om - Ox
    - O'Meara, Carroll., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - O'Sullivan, Rev. Michael P., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Overholser, Wayne D., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Overseas Associates Incorporated., 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - O'Neill, Charles., 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Opitz, Edmund A., 12 items. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Oxford University Press., 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Pa
    - Pacific Coast Writers Conference., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - The Packet., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Page, Al & Sherry., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Panos, Sam., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Parker, Harvey., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Parsons, Homer M., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Pascal, Hannah., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Pacific Spectator., 5 items. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Painter, Cecil., 8 items. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Painter, Landon Cecil & Ellen., 16 items. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Parker, C.C., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Parsons, Charles., 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Pe
    - Peacock, E.P., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Peacock, Mary Thomas., 2 items. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Pearl, Raymond., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Pearman, Betty & Stuart., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Peccolo, William., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Perkerson, Medora Field., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Perry, Bernard P., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Perry, Edward Caswell., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - The Personalist., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Peters, Philip Rising., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Pettis, W.M., 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Pead, Margaret., 3 items. (Box 17, Folder 14)